[
  {"question": "سماء", "answer": "اءمس"},
  {"question": "بحر", "answer": "رحب"},
  {"question": "قهوة", "answer": "ةوهق"},
  {"question": "كتاب", "answer": "باتك"},
  {"question": "مدرسة", "answer": "ةسر دم"},
  {"question": "مدينة", "answer": "ةدينم"},
  {"question": "برج", "answer": "جرب"},
  {"question": "قلم", "answer": "ملق"},
  {"question": "شجرة", "answer": "ةرجش"},
  {"question": "مكتبة", "answer": "ةبت كم"}
]
